[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":81585,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":843209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":17534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":860748,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":4364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":865112,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":6657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":871771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2826,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":874597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8579,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":883185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1368,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":884555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6578,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":891133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1252,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":892385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":897221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2072,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":899293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5056,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":904350,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1480,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":905830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":910768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":912716,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perf orm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4796,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":917514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":919498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":926333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3758,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":930093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":937683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1144,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":938829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":31783,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":970618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). S imilarly , 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":173917,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":1144537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":13736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":1158274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":38962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":1197239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Remembe r, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":12892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":1210132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":26131,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1236265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1239686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":9171,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1248859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3086,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1251946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2643,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1254589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is  the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3930,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1258520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":8926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1267447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":45372,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1312820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":80580,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1393401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1403119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":19878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1423030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1429800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":14785,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1444601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1449534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator  under + <sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":16569,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1466103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4619,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1470723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":19188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1489913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some ques tions ab out a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19247,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1509160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":8303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1517465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":5623,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1523088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1528509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1533862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1541096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1544695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1549004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1553746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1558296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the answer. If the result is 9 or above then subtract 9 to get the answer.","response_history":["Add two numbers. i","Add two numbers. If the resutl","Add two numbers. If the resut","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the anser. ","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the anser.","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the anser","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the anse","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the answer. If the result is n","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the answer. If the result is 9 or above then substract 9 to get  the ans wer.","Add two numbers. If the result is under nine then that is the answer. If the result is 9 or above then subtract 9 to get the answer."],"rt":50687,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1608985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":16385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1625370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1631218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free ","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 I add what it would take to get 9","response_history":["6 I add the ","6 I add the","6 I add th","6 I add to the fir","6 I add to the fi","6 I add to the f","6 I add to the ","6 I add what it would take to get n","6 I add what it would take to get 9"],"rt":27897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1659115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, I'm not sure. I don't understand this one","response_history":["Yes, I'm not sure. I don' tun","Yes, I'm not sure. I don' tu","Yes, I'm not sure. I don' t","Yes, I'm not sure. I don' ","Yes, I'm not sure. I don't understand this one"],"rt":23243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1682374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0 "},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. Not sure how","response_history":["Yea","Yes. Not sure how"],"rt":10337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1692711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. I don't know","response_history":["Yes. I don't know"],"rt":7000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1699728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't know","response_history":["No,","No. I don't know"],"rt":9759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1709487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":25611,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1735101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n=0","response_history":["1=n","1=","1+n=0"],"rt":23985,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1759086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an elem ent x un der +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"X+n=0 The inverse will equal 0","response_history":["X+n=0 The inversw","X+n=0 The inverse will equal 0"],"rt":37528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1796614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"You would have to know what x is.","response_history":["You woul dha","You woul dh","You woul d","You woul ","You would have to know what x is."],"rt":194275,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1990889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it mus t be a g enerator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1997194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2005040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":10012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2015052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. I'm not sure","response_history":["G","False. I'm not sure"],"rt":46693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2061747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":91333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2153080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a genera tor unde r +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"It depends on what the number is","response_history":["It den","It depends on what the number is"],"rt":13411,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2166491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":24298,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2190791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2918,"trial_type":" instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2193709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2196600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3122,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2199724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes a nd you'r e not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 1","response_history":["Algebra 1"],"rt":14285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2214012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2219795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of i t","2 -  heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2223805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":7749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2231556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - n ot at all"],"rt":4881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2236437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2240342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1963,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2242305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"eng lish","response_history":["english"],"rt":6333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2248638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":4776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2253414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":5426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2258840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]